http://www.grandecheese.com/privacy-policy/

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Grande Cheese Company Privacy Policy
This website is owned and operated by Grande Cheese Company. Here at Grande, we recognize that many visitors to our website are concerned about the information they provide to us, how we treat that information, and who receives that information. We’ve provided this Privacy Policy to explain our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.
PLEASE NOTE BY ACCESSING OR USING THIS WEBSITE, YOU ARE AGREEING TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION AS DISCUSSED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT ACCESS THIS WEBSITE.
We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. We will indicate the Policy’s effective date on the first page of the Policy. All changes will be effective immediately upon their posting to this website. Material changes will be conspicuously posted on this website. BY ACCESSING OR USING THIS WEBSITE AFTER SUCH CHANGES ARE POSTED YOU AGREE AND CONSENT TO ALL SUCH CHANGES.
Types of Information We Collect
How Information is Collected
Personally-Identifiable information
Contests and Promotions
Questionnaires and Surveys
Aggregated Information
Cookies
Web Beacons
Types of Information We Collect
At our website, we may collect both personally-identifiable information and aggregate information that is not personally-identifiable.
Personally-identifiable information relates to you as an individual – e.g., name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, demographic information, credit card number, company information, information required to complete an order or your registration, etc. We only collect personally-identifiable information from individuals who provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly, such as by registering on our website to access certain portions of our website, or by requesting follow-up contacts or other information or materials from us.
Aggregate information relates to such things as how many consumers visit the website, which pages are most commonly accessed, what information is downloaded, the type of web browser and operating system you use, the name of your Internet Service Provider (e.g., America Online), and so on. When you visit our website, we may automatically collect this information, and combine it with similar information collected about all other visitors. By collecting this information, we learn how to best tailor our website to our visitors and enhance your experience on our website.
How Information is Collected
Personally-Identifiable Information
As we noted above, personally-identifiable information is collected from you directly and with your knowledge. Thus, when you register on the website to access certain members-only portions of the website, we collect the information you provide during the registration process. When you enter a promotion or request services or information from us, we collect the information needed for you to participate and for us to fulfill our obligations to you. When you e-mail us, we collect the e-mail address you supply, and any other information in your e-mail, so that we can respond.
Contests and Sweepstakes
Our website sometimes includes notices of contests or promotions we are conducting. In some instances, we may permit you to enter such promotions electronically in some cases. If that occurs, we will use the information you provide for the purpose of conducting the promotion (e.g., to contact you if you’re a winner). Within a reasonable time after the conclusion of the promotion, the personal information will be deleted from our database, unless you’ve agreed to permit us to keep it and use it to contact you again. Any such contest or promotion will also be subject to any additional contest or promotion rules.
Questionnaires and Surveys
We may occasionally ask visitors to complete surveys and opinion polls about their attitudes and interests. Surveys help us to understand your business needs and how we can help serve those needs. If sample answers to surveys are posted on the website, no personally identifiable information will be included without your express consent.
Aggregated Information
We may also collect non-personal information when you view our website which is used on an aggregated basis. The collection of this non-personal information may be done either through “cookie” technology or with “web beacons” (also called ‘single-pixel gifs’) or tracking internet protocol (IP) addresses, as explained below.
Cookies
Like many companies, we may also use “cookie” technology on and off of our website. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. They enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular website. The cookies do not contain any personally-identifiable information and cannot profile your system or collect information from your hard drive.
When you view our website we may place a “cookie” on your computer. Temporary cookies are used for purposes such as counting the number of visits to our websites. These temporary cookies are eliminated when you exit your browser. A permanent cookie may also be stored on your computer by your browser. When you log in, this type of cookie tells us whether you’ve visited us before or if you are a new visitor. The cookie doesn’t obtain any personal information about you or provide us with any way to contact you, and the cookie doesn’t extract any information from your computer.
The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Remember, though, that disabling this function may impact your use and enjoyment of this website.
Web Beacons
Web beacons are Internet tools, such as transparent images on the website or in e-mails that we may send you, that help us to determine, for instance, whether a page has been viewed or an e-mail opened. For example, when you ask us to send you information on a promotion or newsletter, we may use web beacons to determine how many of the e-mails we sent were actually opened. In general, any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including a banner ad, can contain a web beacon.
Third party advertising networks that serve ads onto any Grande website may use cookies and/or web beacons in their advertisements. Grande retains no control over these third party cookies and/or web beacons and does not have access to whatever information they may collect on behalf of the third party. To learn more about third party advertising networks and their privacy policies, click here http://www.networkadvertising.org/.
In addition, Grande may use cookies and/or web beacons when Grande advertises on other companies’ websites. Any information we gather in this way will be governed by this Privacy Policy.
IP Addresses
We may also log IP addresses for systems administration purposes. IP addresses are not used to track a user’s session. This information only helps us determine how often different areas of our website are visited. We do not link IP address to any information that is personally identifiable.
How We Use Your Personal Information
We may use the personal information you provide us to provide you with the services or information that you request from us or respond to your comments or questions. For example, we may contact you if needed in the course of processing a product or service you requested through our website. In addition, if you complete the registration process to access certain portions of our website, or if you purchase anything from our website, you will be asked if we can contact you in the future. If you agree to such follow-up contacts, we may put you on our mailing list or otherwise contact you from time to time. For example, we may occasionally send you marketing or promotion materials.
In the e-mail section of our website, we may ask for some personally-identifiable information, such as your name and phone number. We use this information only if we need to contact you directly because our attempts to contact you by e-mail were unsuccessful. We don’t use your e-mail address for any purpose other than responding to your request, unless we have your permission.
We also may use your personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze website usage, and to improve our features and content. We may also use your personal information to deliver content that is customized to your interests, as we best understand them from the information you’ve provided to us and your activities on the website. This customized content may include such things as recipes, banners, product information, and promotions.
Finally, although we do not collect personal information automatically, we may combine non-personal information collected automatically (through cookies) with your previously submitted personal information.
Third Parties Who Provide Support Services to Grande
In the course of doing business, we may employ third-party companies and individuals to perform a variety of functions on our behalf. For example, we may hire agencies to help administer consumer promotions, to analyze data, to fulfill orders you place, or to provide customer service. These third parties may have access to your personal information solely to the extent it is needed to perform their functions for Grande or otherwise to provide you with the services or information that you may request; however, they are prohibited from using it for other purposes and they are required to maintain the information in confidence.
Data Ownership, Sharing and Transfer
We do not otherwise sell, rent, or loan the personally-identifiable information we gather on our website to third parties without your prior consent. However, we reserve the right to use, share, and disclose your personal information in the event we believe doing so is necessary to operate this website or otherwise provide you with the services and information you may request, where such disclosure may be required by law, or to protect our rights or the rights of others.
There may be times when we share aggregate information about our visitors (for example, the percentage of male and female visitors to our website, web browsers/operating systems used by our visitors, pages visited, etc.) with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties in an effort to customize or enhance the content and advertising of our website for our users.
Grande maintains full rights to any information collected on this website, and may freely collect, use and disclose such information unless prohibited by this Privacy Policy or applicable law. In the event of a change in control of Grande or sale by Grande of substantially all of its assets, any information owned by or in the control of Grande may be transferred to such company successor, who will comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Security of Information
This website has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However, we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to information will not occur. In the event that a breach into our security systems occurs and there is a possibility that an unauthorized person acquires your personal information, we will notify you of such a breach under applicable law.
Links to Other Websites
Grande may offer links to third-party websites that we believe may be helpful to you. However, we do not maintain such websites nor do we endorse the content of any such websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third parties or third-party websites, including any linked or linking websites. To the extent that you disclose personally identifiable information to any such third parties, different rules may apply to their use and disclosure of personal information that you disclose to them. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of such websites before disclosing your personal information to them to understand your rights.
Grande maintains full rights to any information collected on this website, and may freely collect, use and disclose such information unless prohibited by this Privacy Policy or applicable law. In the event of a change in control of Grande or sale by Grande of substantially all of its assets, any information owned by or in the control of Grande may be transferred to such company successor, who will comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Security of Information
This website has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However, we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to information will not occur. In the event that a breach into our security systems occurs and there is a possibility that an unauthorized person acquires your personal information, we will notify you of such a breach under applicable law.
Links to Other Websites
Grande may offer links to third-party websites that we believe may be helpful to you. However, we do not maintain such websites nor do we endorse the content of any such websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third parties or third-party websites, including any linked or linking websites. To the extent that you disclose personally identifiable information to any such third parties, different rules may apply to their use and disclosure of personal information that you disclose to them. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of such websites before disclosing your personal information to them to understand your rights.
Choice and Control
You are ultimately in control of the personally-identifiable information you provide to us on our website. You can always change your preference for follow-up contacts just by e-mailing the Online Team at the address listed below or, if you are a registered user, by changing the information in Your Profile section of the website. If you prefer, you can cancel your registration altogether and we will take prompt steps to remove your personally-identifiable information from our database. You may also request that we update your personal information or correct any factual errors that you believe may exist regarding this information. Please contact us with your request at 800-8-GRANDE or marketing@grande.com with any questions regarding your information.
Important Note Regarding Children
This website is not directed toward children under 13 years of age and Grande does not knowingly collect or use information from children under 13 through this website.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:
Grande Cheese Company
250 Camelot Drive
Fond du Lac, WI 54935
800-8-GRANDE
(8 a.m. – 4 p.m. Central Time, Monday through Friday.)
or Email us at marketing@grande.com
We’ll be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns.
